OH, HEY,
YOU GUYS, LOOK.
UGLY NAKED GUY'S
PUTTING STUFF IN BOXES.
HUH... I'D SAY
FROM THE LOOKS OF IT
OUR NAKED BUDDY
IS MOVING.
IRONICALLY, MOST OF THE BOXES
SEEM TO BE LABELED "CLOTHES."
AAH, I'M GOING TO MISS
THAT BIG, OLD, SQUISHY BUTT.
AND WE'RE DONE
WITH THE CHICKEN FRIED RICE.
HEY!
HEY, IF HE'S MOVING
MAYBE I SHOULD TRY
TO GET HIS PLACE.
OH, GOOD IDEA.
YES.
IT'LL BE SO COOL
TO LIVE ACROSS
FROM YOU GUYS.
YEAH, HEY, THEN
WE COULD DO THAT
TELEPHONE THING--
YOU KNOW, WELL,
YOU HAVE A CAN
WE HAVE A CAN
AND IT'S CONNECTED
BY A STRING.
OR WE COULD DO THE
ACTUAL TELEPHONE THING.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY,
YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH ♪
♪ OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OH, MY GOD,
I LOVE THIS APARTMENT.
ISN'T IT PERFECT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I NEVER REALIZED
HOW-HOW GREAT IT IS.
WELL, THAT IS BECAUSE
YOUR EYE IMMEDIATELY GOES
TO THE BIG NAKED MAN.
Phoebe:
IT'S AMAZING.
YOU'D BETTER HURRY UP
AND FILL OUT AN APPLICATION,
OR I'M GOING TO BEAT YOU TO IT.
( giggling ):
OH.
WELL, I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SAY THIS
BUT I'M GOING TO GO USE
UGLY NAKED GUY'S BATHROOM.
YEAH.
OH, LOOK,
THERE'S MONICA AND CHANDLER.
HEY!
HEY, YOU GUYS! HEY!
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
WHAT?
AAH! CHANDLER
AND MONICA!
CHANDLER AND MONICA!
OH, MY GOD!
AAH!
CHANDLER AND MONICA!
OH, MY GOD!
OH!
OH, MY EYES!
MY EYES!
OH, PHOEBE!
PHOEBE...
OW!
OKAY! IT'S OKAY!
IT'S OKAY!
NO, THEY'RE DOING IT!
I KNOW! I KNOW!
YOU KNOW?!
YES, I KNOW
AND JOEY KNOWS!
BUT ROSS
DOESN'T KNOW!
SO YOU HAVE TO
STOP SCREAMING!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH!
( yelling )
WHAT? WHAT?
NOTHING. OH, GOD,
WE'RE JUST SO EXCITED
THAT YOU MIGHT
GET THIS APARTMENT!
YEAH, IT LOOKS
REALLY GOOD...
OH, MY GOD!
GET IN HERE!
COME ON!
( all yelling )
YOU MEAN, WHENEVER
MONICA AND CHANDLER
WERE, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"DOING LAUNDRY"
OR GOING "GROCERY SHOPPING..."
ALL THAT TIME MONICA
SPENT ON THE PHONE
WITH "SAD LINDA FROM CAMP"?
DOING IT. DOING IT.
PHONE DOING IT.
OH!
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I MEAN, I THINK IT'S GREAT...
FOR HIM.
SHE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO DO BETTER.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
JOEY, COME HERE!
PHOEBE JUST
FOUND OUT
ABOUT MONICA AND CHANDLER.
YOU MEAN, HOW
THEY'RE FRIENDS
AND NOTHING MORE?
NO.
NO. JOEY, SHE KNOWS.
WE WERE AT UGLY
NAKED GUY'S APARTMENT
AND WE SAW THEM DOING IT
THROUGH THE WINDOW.
ACTUALLY, WE SAW THEM
DOING IT UP AGAINST THE WINDOW.
OKAY, SO NOW,
THEY KNOW
YOU KNOW AND THEY DON'T KNOW
THAT RACHEL KNOWS?
YES, BUT...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO KNOWS WHAT.
NOW ENOUGH OF US KNOW
THAT WE COULD JUST
TELL THEM WE KNOW.
NOW ALL THE LYING
AND THE SECRETS
WILL FINALLY BE OVER.
OR WE COULD
NOT TELL THEM WE KNOW
AND HAVE A LITTLE FUN
OF OUR OWN.
WH-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
EVERY TIME THAT THEY SAY
THEY'RE DOING LAUNDRY
WE'LL GIVE THEM A BUNCH
OF LAUNDRY TO DO.
OH... I-I WOULD ENJOY THAT.
NO, WAIT. WAIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD
BE EVEN MORE FUN?
TELLING THEM.
YEAH, NO.
I WANT TO DO PHOEBE'S THING.
NO, BUT I CAN'T...
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING.
JUST DON'T TELL THEM
THAT WE KNOW.
NO. I CAN'T TAKE
ANY MORE SECRETS.
I GOT YOUR SECRETS.
I GOT THEIR SECRETS.
I GOT SECRETS OF
MY OWN, YOU KNOW?
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY SECRETS.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU DON'T
KNOW ABOUT HUGGSY--
MY BEDTIME PENGUIN PAL.
SO... UM....
HOW-HOW ARE WE GOING
TO MESS WITH THEM?
( moaning )
WELL, YOU COULD
USE YOUR POSITION
YOU KNOW, AS THE ROOMMATE,
AND THEN I WOULD USE
YOU KNOW, THE STRONGEST TOOL
AT MY DISPOSAL--
MY SEXUALITY.
HELLO, CHILDREN.
HEY.
OKAY, WATCH... LEARN...
AND DON'T EAT MY COOKIE.
HEY.
OOH, WOW, THAT JACKET
LOOKS GREAT ON YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH. THE MATERIAL
LOOKS SO SOFT...
OH, HELLO, MR. BICEP.
HAVE YOU BEEN
WORKING OUT?
WELL, I TRY TO
YOU KNOW, SQUEEZE THINGS.
( giggling )
ARE YOU OKAY?
WELL, IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO KNOW...
I, OH, I CAN'T
TELL YOU THIS.
PHOEBE, IT'S ME--
YOU CAN TELL ME ANYTHING.
ACTUALLY, YOU'RE
THE ONE PERSON
I CAN'T TELL THIS TO
AND THE ONE PERSON
I WANT TO THE MOST.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THINK IT'S JUST
THAT I HAVEN'T BEEN
WITH A GUY IN SO LONG
AND YOU KNOW HOW
SOMETIMES YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
AND YOU JUST DON'T
EVEN SEE THAT'S
IT RIGHT THERE
IN FRONT OF YOU
SIPPING COFFEE...
OH, NO, HAVE I
SAID TOO MUCH?
WELL, JUST SOMETHING
TO THINK ABOUT...
I KNOW I WILL.
OOH...
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
HOW DID YOU GET
TO BE SO CUTE?
WELL
MY GRANDFATHER WAS SWEDISH...
AND MY GRANDMOTHER
WAS, ACTUALLY
A TINY, LITTLE BUNNY.
NOW YOU'RE
EVEN CUTER.
YOU KNOW, THAT IS
A POPULAR OPINION TODAY
I MUST SAY.
WHAT?
THE WEIRDEST THING HAPPENED
AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
I THINK PHOEBE
WAS HITTING ON ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TELLING YOU,
I THINK PHOEBE
THINKS I'M FOXY.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
OW.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST...
I MEAN, PHOEBE HAS
JUST ALWAYS THOUGHT
YOU WERE CHARMING IN
A SEXLESS KIND OF WAY.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
I-I CAN'T HEAR THAT ENOUGH.
I-I'M SORRY.
I JUST THINK THAT
YOU MISUNDERSTOOD HER.
NO. I DIDN'T
MISUNDERSTAND, OKAY?
SHE WAS ALL OVER ME.
SHE TOUCHED MY BICEP,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
THIS BICEP?
WELL, IT'S NOT
FLEXED RIGHT NOW.
HEY, MON, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING NOW?
YOU WANT TO COME
SEE A MOVIE WITH US?
UH... YOU KNOW,
ACTUALLY
I-I WAS GOING
TO DO SOME LAUNDRY.
HEY, CHANDLER
YOU WANT TO DO
IT WITH ME?
SURE, I'LL...
DO IT WITH YOU.
OKAY.
OKAY, GREAT. HOLD ON A SEC.
OH... HERE YOU GO.
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
THAT WOULD REALLY HELP ME
OUT A LOT. THANKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I-I DON'T THINK
I HAVE ENOUGH QUARTERS.
OH, I HAVE QUARTERS.
OH!
HEY.
HEY, ROSS
ANY WORD
ON THE APARTMENT YET?
I CALLED OVER THERE
AND UGLY NAKED GUY
IS SUBLETTING IT HIMSELF
AND HE'S ALREADY HAD
LIKE 100 APPLICANTS.
OH.
OH, MAN.
I'VE GOT THE EDGE.
I KNOW IT'S NOT EXACTLY ETHICAL
BUT I SENT HIM A LITTLE BRIBE
TO TIP THE SCALES
IN MY DIRECTION.
YEAH. CHECK IT OUT.
YOU CAN PROBABLY
SEE IT FROM THE WINDOW.
OH, IS IT THAT
PINBALL MACHINE
WITH THE BIG
BOW ON IT?
NO.
THAT NEW MOUNTAIN BIKE?
WELL, WHAT
DID YOU SEND?
A BASKET OF MINI MUFFINS.
BUT THERE'S A WHOLE TABLE
OF MINI MUFFIN BASKETS
WHICH ONE DID YOU SEND?
THE SMALL ONE.
WHAT? YOU-YOU ACTUALLY
THOUGHT THAT BASKET
WAS GOING TO GET YOU
THE APARTMENT?
WELL... YEAH.
SOMEONE SENT US
A BASKET AT WORK ONCE
AND PEOPLE WENT CRAZY
OVER THOSE LITTLE MUFFINS.
IT WAS THE BEST DAY.
YOUR WORK MAKES ME SAD.
( sighing )
OH, MAN...
I WANT THAT PLACE SO MUCH...
AND I WAS SO SURE
THAT WAS GOING TO WORK.
THERE'S 12 BUCKS
I'LL NEVER SEE AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'D BETTER GO
IF WE'RE GOING
TO CATCH THAT MOVIE.
BYE.
BYE, CHANDLER.
I MISS YOU ALREADY.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
WITH THE INAPPROPRIATE
AND THE PINCHING?
ACTUALLY, I DID.
OKAY, SO NOW
DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT SHE'S
ATTRACTED TO ME?
( gasping ):
OH, MY GOD...
OH, MY GOD,
SHE KNOWS ABOUT US!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
PHOEBE KNOWS, AND SHE'S
JUST TRYING TO FREAK US OUT.
THAT'S THE ONLY
EXPLANATION FOR IT.
OKAY, BUT WHAT
ABOUT MY PINCHABLE BUTT
AND MY BULGING BICEPS?
SHE KNOWS!
JOEY!
YEAH?!
PHOEBE KNOWS
ABOUT US.
WELL, I DIDN'T TELL THEM.
"THEM"?
WHO'S "THEM"?
UH... PHOEBE AND JOEY.
JOEY.
AND RACHEL.
I WOULD HAVE TOLD YOU
BUT THEY MADE ME
PROMISE NOT TO.
OH, MAN!
I'M SORRY, BUT, HEY,
IT'S OVER NOW, RIGHT?
'CAUSE YOU CAN TELL THEM
YOU KNOW THEY KNOW
AND I CAN GO BACK
TO KNOWING ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
UNLESS...
NO, NOT UNLESS.
THIS MUST END NOW!
OH, MAN, THEY THINK
THEY ARE SO SLICK
MESSING WITH US.
BUT SEE, THEY DON'T
KNOW THAT WE KNOW
THAT THEY KNOW.
SO...
AH, YES.
THE MESSERS BECOME
THE MESSEES!
( groans )
OH, ROSS, HONEY,
YOU GOT TO STOP
TORTURING YOURSELF.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST FIND
ANOTHER APARTMENT?
I'VE ALREADY
LOOKED AT, LIKE
A THOUSAND
APARTMENTS
THIS MONTH
AND NONE OF THEM
EVEN COMPARES TO THAT ONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SHOULD DO?
YOU SHOULD FIND OUT
WHAT HIS HOBBIES ARE
AND THEN USE THAT
TO BOND WITH HIM.
YEAH. LIKE IF I WANTED
SOMETHING FROM JOEY
I WOULD STRIKE UP
A CONVERSATION
ABOUT, SAY, UM, SANDWICHES...
OR, UH, OR MY UNDERWEAR.
I'M LISTENING.
SEE?
THAT IS A GREAT IDEA.
AND I KNOW UGLY NAKED GUY
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN WATCHING HIM
FOR, LIKE, FIVE YEARS
SO THAT GIVES ME BACK MY EDGE.
LET'S SEE NOW.
HE HAD THE TRAMPOLINE.
HE BROKE THAT.
WELL, HE HAD GRAVITY BOOTS.
YEAH, HE BROKE
THOSE, TOO.
SO HE LIKES
TO BREAK STUFF.
OKAY, I'VE GOT
TO GO PICK UP BEN
BUT I WILL FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
HEY, DIDN'T HE USED
TO HAVE A CAT?
I WOULDN'T BRING THAT UP.
IT'D PROBABLY
JUST BUM HIM OUT.
POOR CAT NEVER SAW
THAT BIG BUTT COMING.
( phone rings )
HELLO.
OH, YEAH. HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND.
SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
IT'S CHANDLER.
OH?
( sultry ):
HELLO, YOU.
HELLO, PHOEBE, I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT YOU ALL DAY.
HUH?
WELL, YOU KNOW
THAT THING YOU
SAID BEFORE.
I'D BE LYING IF I SAID
I WASN'T INTRIGUED.
REALLY?
Yeah, listen
JOEY'S NOT GOING
TO BE HERE TONIGHT
SO WHY DON'T
YOU COME OVER
AND I'LL LET
YOU FEEL MY BICEP.
OR MAYBE MORE.
I'LL HAVE TO GET BACK TO YOU
ON THAT.
OKAY, BYE.
OH, MY GOD.
HE WANTS ME TO COME OVER
AND FEEL HIS BICEP AND MORE.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
HE WOULD DO THAT TO MON...
WA...
JOEY, DO THEY KNOW THAT WE KNOW?
NO.
JOEY?
THEY KNOW YOU KNOW.
OH! I KNEW IT!
OH! I CANNOT BELIEVE
THOSE TWO!
THEY THOUGHT THAT THEY
COULD MESS WITH US.
THEY'RE TRYING
TO MESS WITH US?!
THEY DON'T KNOW THAT WE
KNOW THEY KNOW WE KNOW.
JOEY, YOU CAN'T
SAY ANYTHING.
I COULDN'T IF I WANTED TO.
GOOD EVENING, SIR.
MY NAME IS ROSS GELLER.
I'M ONE OF THE PEOPLE WHO
APPLIED FOR THE APARTMENT
AND I REALIZE THAT
THE COMPETITION IS
FIERCE, BUT...
I'M SORRY.
I-I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
THAT YOU'RE NAKED AND...
I APPLAUD YOU.
MAN, I WISH I WAS NAKED.
I MEAN, THIS, THIS
LOOKS SO GREAT.
THAT IS HOW GOD
INTENDED IT.
LOOK AT THEM.
THEY'RE PANICKED.
OH, YEAH. THEY'LL
TOTALLY BACK DOWN.
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
IF HE WANTS A DATE,
HE'S GOING TO GET A DATE.
ALL RIGHT. I'M
GOING TO GO IN.
OKAY. OKAY. BE SEXY.
PLEASE.
( stutters )
SO, CHANDLER, I'D LOVE
TO COME BY TONIGHT.
REALLY?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
SHOULD WE SAY
AROUND 7:00?
YES.
GOOD.
I'M REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD
TO YOU AND ME HAVING
SEXUAL INTERCOURSE.
( no audio )
HEY, HEY. CHECK IT OUT.
CHECK IT OUT.
UGLY NAKED GUY'S GOT
A NAKED FRIEND.
OH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S OUR FRIEND!
IT'S NAKED ROSS!
IT IS ROSS!
SHOW TIME!
OKAY, RACHEL
GET ME PERFUME.
OKAY.
AND, JOEY, COULD YOU GET ME
A BOTTLE OF WINE AND GLASSES?
OKAY.
IT'LL BE GREAT.
JUST MAKE HER THINK
YOU WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH HER.
IT'LL TOTALLY
FREAK HER OUT.
OKAY, LISTEN, HOW
FAR AM I GOING TO
HAVE TO GO WITH HER?
RELAX. SHE'S GOING TO GIVE IN
WAY BEFORE YOU DO.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE YOU'RE ON MY TEAM
AND MY TEAM ALWAYS WINS.
AT THIS?
JUST GO GET SOME.
GO!
OKAY, HONEY. NOW,
I'M GOING TO TRY TO
LISTEN FROM RIGHT HERE.
OKAY.
OKAY?
OH, WAIT.
GOOD IDEA.
YEAH. OH, WAIT.
DON'T GIVE AWAY THE FARM.
OKAY.
PHOEBE.
CHANDLER.
COME ON IN.
I WAS GOING TO.
UM, I BROUGHT SOME WINE.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME?
SURE.
OH.
SO, HERE WE ARE.
NERVOUS?
ME? NO. YOU?
NO. I WANT THIS TO HAPPEN.
SO DO I.
( chuckles )
I'M GOING TO PUT ON SOME MUSIC.
MAYBE, MAYBE I'LL DANCE FOR YOU.
( music plays )
YOU LOOK GOOD.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU
SAY THINGS LIKE THAT
IT MAKES ME WANT
TO RIP THAT SWEATER
VEST RIGHT OFF.
WELL, WHY DON'T WE MOVE THIS
INTO THE BEDROOM?
REALLY?
OH, DO YOU NOT WANT TO?
NO, NO.
I JUST, YOU KNOW
FIRST, I WANT
TO TAKE OFF
ALL MY CLOTHES
AND HAVE YOU RUB
LOTION ON ME.
( stumbling ):
WELL, THAT WOULD BE NICE.
I'LL GO GET THE LOTION.
THIS IS TOTALLY GETTING
OUT OF HAND, OKAY?
SHE WANTS ME TO
PUT LOTION ON HER!
SHE'S BLUFFING!
LOOK, SHE'S NOT
BACKING DOWN.
SHE WENT LIKE THIS:
H-H-HE'S NOT BACKING DOWN.
HE WENT TO GET LOTION.
( door opens )
OH, MAN, AREN'T
YOU GUYS DONE YET?
I WANT TO SIT
IN MY CHAIR.
JUST LOOK
AT IT THIS WAY.
THE SOONER PHOEBE
BREAKS CHANDLER
THE SOONER THIS IS ALL
OVER AND OUT IN THE OPEN.
OOH, I LIKE THAT.
OH, OKAY, SHOW
HIM YOUR BRA.
HE'S AFRAID OF BRAS.
CAN'T WORK 'EM.
JOEY!
WOW, YOU DIDN'T RIP
OFF ANY BUTTONS.
NOT MY FIRST TIME.
YOU GO BACK OUT THERE
AND YOU SEDUCE HER
TILL SHE CRACKS.
OKAY. GIVE ME A SECOND.
DID YOU CLEAN UP IN HERE?
OF COURSE.
OH, YOU'RE GOING?
NOT WITHOUT YOU, LOVER.
SO, THIS IS MY BRA.
IT'S VERY, VERY NICE.
WELL, COME HERE.
I'M VERY HAPPY WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE ALL THE SEX.
YOU SHOULD BE.
I'M VERY BENDY.
I'M GOING TO KISS YOU NOW.
NOT IF I KISS YOU FIRST.
WELL, I GUESS THERE'S NOTHING
LEFT FOR US TO DO BUT KISS.
HERE IT COMES.
OUR FIRST KISS.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
FINE! YOU WIN!
I CAN'T HAVE
SEX WITH YOU.
AND WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I'M IN LOVE WITH MONICA.
YOU-YOU'RE WHAT?
Chandler:
LOVE HER!
THAT'S RIGHT! I LOVE HER!
I LOVE HER!
I LOVE YOU, MONICA.
I LOVE YOU,
TOO, CHANDLER.
I JUST... I THOUGHT
YOU GUYS WERE DOING IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE IN LOVE.
DUDE!
AND HATS OFF
TO PHOEBE.
QUITE A COMPETITOR.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
AND MAY I SAY
YOUR BREASTS ARE
STILL SHOWING?
GOD.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, THAT'S IT.
IT'S OVER.
EVERYBODY KNOWS.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
ROSS DOESN'T.
YES, AND WE'D APPRECIATE IT
IF NO ONE TOLD HIM YET.
A NEW PLACE
FOR A NEW ROSS.
I'LL HAVE YOU AND ALL
THE GUYS FROM WORK OVER
ONCE IT'S, YOU
KNOW, FURNISHED.
I MUST SAY, IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU
BACK ON YOUR FEET.
WELL, I AM THAT.
AND THAT WHOLE RAGE THING
IS DEFINITELY BEHIND ME.
I WONDER IF IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO REJOIN OUR TEAM
AT THE MUSEUM.
OH, DONALD,
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
I AM TOTALLY READY
TO COME BACK TO WORK.
I... WHAT?
NO.
WHA...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GET OFF MY SISTER!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]